# **AARON ARGUELLES - FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Wellsville, UT | 435-994-4203 | arguelles.business@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Software Engineer proficient in using JavaScript for front-end and back-end programming, React, HTML, CSS/SCSS, API implementing, Node.JS, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, and frameworks like Bootstrap and Tailwind. Experience in team and leadership roles provides an advantage in discovering and implementing solutions to problems.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Frontend: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, React, Astro, Handlebars.js, TypeScript

Backend: Node.js, RESTful APIs, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, Strapi

Tools: BigCommerce, Stencil, DigitalOcean, Visual Studio Code, ClickUp, Figma, Node Package Manager, Yarn,

Git, GitHub, ADA/WCAG Compliance

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Malouf Companies

Logan, UT

Web Developer 1 Jr. Web Developer 03/2024 - Present 09/2023 - 03/2024

- Took on the role of lead developer for multiple website redesigns and directed team to specific tasks.
- Completed development tasks according to a sprint schedule.
- Wrote code compliant with ADA/WCAG AA 2.2+.
- Worked cross-functionally with design and content departments to develop user interfaces, reusable components, and changes to data entry.
- Partnered with marketing and sales teams to translate business objectives into actionable code.
- Collaborated with teammates to create implementation plans and best practices.
- Effectively prioritized work to accommodate ad-hoc support to internal clients.
- Contributed quality code as well as documentation.
- Participated in code reviews, team and new employee trainings, testing, and overall morale.

#### **EDUCATION**

Thinkful

Online

#### Certificate, Software Engineering

04/2023 - 09/2023

- Learned industry best practices and software development standards with a focus on JavaScript, HTML5,
  CSS3, React Native, Node.js, PostgreSQL, RESTful API's, algorithms, and data structures.
- Developed and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks, spending several hours per week collaborating with senior web developers in a mentor-student relationship.